[
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0915,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob019.pddl",
    "runtime": 602.6504981517792
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0743,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob015.pddl",
    "runtime": 602.5334994792938
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.1103,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob044.pddl",
    "runtime": 603.9083995819092
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0925,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob024.pddl",
    "runtime": 603.5646810531616
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0369,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob004.pddl",
    "runtime": 603.1648581027985
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0996,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob030.pddl",
    "runtime": 603.8682272434235
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.078,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob010.pddl",
    "runtime": 604.3766946792603
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0974,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob043.pddl",
    "runtime": 605.3388423919678
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 16,
    "p_success": 0.5482,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob002.pddl",
    "runtime": 604.516250371933
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0263,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob020.pddl",
    "runtime": 624.927252292633
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 29,
    "p_success": 0.9008,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob021.pddl",
    "runtime": 623.418093919754
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 49,
    "p_success": 0.4386,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob036.pddl",
    "runtime": 615.9150152206421
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.057,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob035.pddl",
    "runtime": 630.4298572540283
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 21,
    "p_success": 0.3385,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob032.pddl",
    "runtime": 622.5017936229706
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 32,
    "p_success": 0.8973,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob011.pddl",
    "runtime": 624.1605143547058
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 4,
    "p_success": 0.0566,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob029.pddl",
    "runtime": 634.6845352649689
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 27,
    "p_success": 0.6498,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob016.pddl",
    "runtime": 632.4138731956482
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 26,
    "p_success": 0.3355,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob017.pddl",
    "runtime": 627.5019927024841
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 18,
    "p_success": 0.7161,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob006.pddl",
    "runtime": 634.7893171310425
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0136,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob005.pddl",
    "runtime": 642.1308019161224
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 8,
    "p_success": 0.1837,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob014.pddl",
    "runtime": 641.3606967926025
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 20,
    "p_success": 0.3165,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob028.pddl",
    "runtime": 636.8946650028229
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 43,
    "p_success": 0.6,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob031.pddl",
    "runtime": 638.0054297447205
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 9,
    "p_success": 0.2456,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob034.pddl",
    "runtime": 651.2711358070374
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 19,
    "p_success": 0.4249,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob041.pddl",
    "runtime": 654.0783679485321
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0389,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob025.pddl",
    "runtime": 667.4495539665222
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 7,
    "p_success": 0.3127,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob042.pddl",
    "runtime": 669.871753692627
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 22,
    "p_success": 0.5175,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob022.pddl",
    "runtime": 667.7887811660767
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 11,
    "p_success": 0.5002,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob013.pddl",
    "runtime": 679.6284203529358
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 212,
    "p_success": 0.7482,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob001.pddl",
    "runtime": 634.4565622806549
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 7,
    "p_success": 0.3381,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob007.pddl",
    "runtime": 685.2504463195801
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 16,
    "p_success": 0.3947,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob038.pddl",
    "runtime": 685.5820565223694
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0431,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob040.pddl",
    "runtime": 692.5701484680176
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 23,
    "p_success": 0.9972,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob026.pddl",
    "runtime": 725.8430404663086
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 11,
    "p_success": 0.5717,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob012.pddl",
    "runtime": 737.7550947666168
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 7,
    "p_success": 0.2034,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob003.pddl",
    "runtime": 739.290890455246
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 11,
    "p_success": 0.2578,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob018.pddl",
    "runtime": 755.2698485851288
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 4,
    "p_success": 0.2017,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob033.pddl",
    "runtime": 767.8505663871765
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 20,
    "p_success": 0.3963,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob037.pddl",
    "runtime": 790.797874212265
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 3,
    "p_success": 0.0945,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob027.pddl",
    "runtime": 866.7855095863342
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 5,
    "p_success": 0.2237,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob008.pddl",
    "runtime": 945.5822222232819
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 5,
    "p_success": 0.4332,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob023.pddl",
    "runtime": 959.8069643974304
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 3,
    "p_success": 0.1009,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob039.pddl",
    "runtime": 1005.9208726882935
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 3,
    "p_success": 0.2748,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob009.pddl",
    "runtime": 1121.4181303977966
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 3,
    "p_success": 0.1004,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob049.pddl",
    "runtime": 603.2112255096436
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0553,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob050.pddl",
    "runtime": 606.219304561615
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 26,
    "p_success": 0.4208,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob052.pddl",
    "runtime": 610.2027621269226
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0605,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob054.pddl",
    "runtime": 610.2385101318359
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 28,
    "p_success": 0.8617,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob051.pddl",
    "runtime": 633.6791367530823
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0705,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob063.pddl",
    "runtime": 608.295437335968
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 37,
    "p_success": 0.2847,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob046.pddl",
    "runtime": 632.707930803299
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0327,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob060.pddl",
    "runtime": 620.2415311336517
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0682,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob059.pddl",
    "runtime": 625.6247210502625
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 35,
    "p_success": 0.3714,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob047.pddl",
    "runtime": 646.1022291183472
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 73,
    "p_success": 0.7193,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob056.pddl",
    "runtime": 624.2409121990204
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 25,
    "p_success": 0.4735,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob057.pddl",
    "runtime": 640.9836242198944
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 15,
    "p_success": 0.8914,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob066.pddl",
    "runtime": 632.031393289566
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob075.pddl",
    "runtime": 601.1281855106354
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0162,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob045.pddl",
    "runtime": 689.1360669136047
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 45,
    "p_success": 0.2741,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob064.pddl",
    "runtime": 632.4728548526764
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0178,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob069.pddl",
    "runtime": 642.8581345081329
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.1047,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob074.pddl",
    "runtime": 620.8558430671692
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 98,
    "p_success": 0.7659,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob061.pddl",
    "runtime": 638.7042896747589
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 30,
    "p_success": 0.8138,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob071.pddl",
    "runtime": 627.3416712284088
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 10,
    "p_success": 0.2757,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob048.pddl",
    "runtime": 732.2521233558655
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 86,
    "p_success": 0.7015,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob076.pddl",
    "runtime": 639.4191086292267
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 6,
    "p_success": 0.4697,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob078.pddl",
    "runtime": 622.8722021579742
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0269,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob079.pddl",
    "runtime": 617.8268496990204
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0278,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob055.pddl",
    "runtime": 741.8481168746948
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.1324,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob082.pddl",
    "runtime": 604.2509412765503
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 3,
    "p_success": 0.3865,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob058.pddl",
    "runtime": 744.8613173961639
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0248,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob065.pddl",
    "runtime": 774.4149074554443
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0219,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob080.pddl",
    "runtime": 681.3309154510498
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 8,
    "p_success": 0.4464,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob067.pddl",
    "runtime": 773.2851686477661
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 13,
    "p_success": 0.8885,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob081.pddl",
    "runtime": 678.3141350746155
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 2,
    "p_success": 0.2161,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob062.pddl",
    "runtime": 825.3779006004333
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 6,
    "p_success": 0.9261,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob072.pddl",
    "runtime": 841.8846569061279
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 2,
    "p_success": 0.2911,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob068.pddl",
    "runtime": 873.0248310565948
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0663,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob085.pddl",
    "runtime": 622.9538223743439
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0368,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob084.pddl",
    "runtime": 725.1535270214081
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 2,
    "p_success": 0.3421,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob073.pddl",
    "runtime": 942.4776785373688
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 102,
    "p_success": 0.7252,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob086.pddl",
    "runtime": 644.8402194976807
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 34,
    "p_success": 0.8873,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob087.pddl",
    "runtime": 640.7574865818024
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 2,
    "p_success": 0.1571,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob077.pddl",
    "runtime": 965.3474230766296
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 2,
    "p_success": 0.1255,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob053.pddl",
    "runtime": 1081.2460629940033
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 3,
    "p_success": 0.1085,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob088.pddl",
    "runtime": 623.6580357551575
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 2,
    "p_success": 0.1249,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob083.pddl",
    "runtime": 988.6584470272064
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0076,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob070.pddl",
    "runtime": 1124.3928408622742
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 15,
    "p_success": 0.688,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob091.pddl",
    "runtime": 619.3599832057953
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0303,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob089.pddl",
    "runtime": 644.3299224376678
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob095.pddl",
    "runtime": 602.3276991844177
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 32,
    "p_success": 0.8847,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob092.pddl",
    "runtime": 629.3888938426971
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 23,
    "p_success": 0.7572,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob096.pddl",
    "runtime": 614.4174733161926
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 9,
    "p_success": 0.509,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob093.pddl",
    "runtime": 635.5887935161591
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0564,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob094.pddl",
    "runtime": 639.4731018543243
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0506,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob099.pddl",
    "runtime": 620.7058627605438
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob004.pddl",
    "runtime": 603.391687631607
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0177,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob090.pddl",
    "runtime": 690.6817789077759
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob005.pddl",
    "runtime": 603.2255439758301
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 26,
    "p_success": 0.5689,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob001.pddl",
    "runtime": 633.676896572113
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 9,
    "p_success": 0.6169,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob098.pddl",
    "runtime": 665.1668717861176
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.1355,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob003.pddl",
    "runtime": 640.9857409000397
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob009.pddl",
    "runtime": 603.5429756641388
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob010.pddl",
    "runtime": 603.7820839881897
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0349,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob100.pddl",
    "runtime": 670.8327083587646
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0338,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob008.pddl",
    "runtime": 647.6410458087921
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob014.pddl",
    "runtime": 603.3217577934265
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob015.pddl",
    "runtime": 603.3610363006592
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 5,
    "p_success": 0.4156,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob006.pddl",
    "runtime": 682.9095776081085
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 49,
    "p_success": 0.9497,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob011.pddl",
    "runtime": 653.7292196750641
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob019.pddl",
    "runtime": 603.1444079875946
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob020.pddl",
    "runtime": 603.5571048259735
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0449,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob018.pddl",
    "runtime": 647.5919942855835
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 70,
    "p_success": 0.9318,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob016.pddl",
    "runtime": 669.1988406181335
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 10,
    "p_success": 0.2294,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob007.pddl",
    "runtime": 818.2608587741852
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob024.pddl",
    "runtime": 607.6256155967712
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 2,
    "p_success": 0.3385,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob002.pddl",
    "runtime": 940.4757299423218
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob025.pddl",
    "runtime": 607.5409905910492
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0409,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob013.pddl",
    "runtime": 879.3628642559052
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob028.pddl",
    "runtime": 606.1946971416473
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.1451,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob022.pddl",
    "runtime": 738.2779469490051
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob029.pddl",
    "runtime": 607.3921003341675
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 2,
    "p_success": 0.1282,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/smallprobs/smallprob097.pddl",
    "runtime": 1053.8034279346466
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 3,
    "p_success": 0.0935,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob017.pddl",
    "runtime": 888.2944002151489
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob030.pddl",
    "runtime": 607.527181148529
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0653,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob027.pddl",
    "runtime": 711.5644497871399
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 14,
    "p_success": 0.8851,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob026.pddl",
    "runtime": 768.3985586166382
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 2,
    "p_success": 0.2153,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob012.pddl",
    "runtime": 1069.494108915329
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 2,
    "p_success": 0.4263,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob021.pddl",
    "runtime": 929.2704062461853
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.3152,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob031.pddl",
    "runtime": 663.9201626777649
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob033.pddl",
    "runtime": 607.9149105548859
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob034.pddl",
    "runtime": 607.3262162208557
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob035.pddl",
    "runtime": 607.9277882575989
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.3912,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob032.pddl",
    "runtime": 676.0167684555054
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob039.pddl",
    "runtime": 607.5398325920105
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob040.pddl",
    "runtime": 608.4420216083527
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 11,
    "p_success": 0.5725,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob036.pddl",
    "runtime": 639.6411371231079
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob043.pddl",
    "runtime": 616.1635296344757
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob044.pddl",
    "runtime": 615.533962726593
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob045.pddl",
    "runtime": 615.4710931777954
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob048.pddl",
    "runtime": 616.4370622634888
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.0386,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob037.pddl",
    "runtime": 686.3293426036835
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob049.pddl",
    "runtime": 615.5299282073975
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob050.pddl",
    "runtime": 615.7442674636841
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob052.pddl",
    "runtime": 609.7989871501923
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 5,
    "p_success": 0.2044,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob041.pddl",
    "runtime": 696.4362087249756
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob053.pddl",
    "runtime": 609.6964342594147
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob054.pddl",
    "runtime": 614.2059237957001
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob055.pddl",
    "runtime": 616.0623531341553
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.135,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob023.pddl",
    "runtime": 1094.1105217933655
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob057.pddl",
    "runtime": 616.0013184547424
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob058.pddl",
    "runtime": 616.3519995212555
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob059.pddl",
    "runtime": 616.8374807834625
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.4254,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob051.pddl",
    "runtime": 807.4800214767456
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob060.pddl",
    "runtime": 615.8391575813293
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob061.pddl",
    "runtime": 634.8395721912384
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob062.pddl",
    "runtime": 634.185866355896
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.1339,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob042.pddl",
    "runtime": 972.6046404838562
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob063.pddl",
    "runtime": 630.758682012558
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.1268,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob038.pddl",
    "runtime": 1007.9903037548065
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob065.pddl",
    "runtime": 633.2012388706207
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob064.pddl",
    "runtime": 634.5757195949554
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob066.pddl",
    "runtime": 635.8539502620697
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob067.pddl",
    "runtime": 632.3235692977905
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob068.pddl",
    "runtime": 634.052586555481
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.2057,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob047.pddl",
    "runtime": 1009.4828040599823
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob069.pddl",
    "runtime": 633.8559622764587
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 2,
    "p_success": 0.9663,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob046.pddl",
    "runtime": 1065.5922966003418
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob070.pddl",
    "runtime": 635.7457814216614
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 1,
    "p_success": 0.4264,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob056.pddl",
    "runtime": 941.0774555206299
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob071.pddl",
    "runtime": 632.9418079853058
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob072.pddl",
    "runtime": 633.6435723304749
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob073.pddl",
    "runtime": 632.7534809112549
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob074.pddl",
    "runtime": 633.8288173675537
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob075.pddl",
    "runtime": 631.6016993522644
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob076.pddl",
    "runtime": 632.0998091697693
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob078.pddl",
    "runtime": 632.7569007873535
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 2,
    "p_success": 0.2635,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob077.pddl",
    "runtime": 654.7916417121887
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob079.pddl",
    "runtime": 633.0695641040802
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob080.pddl",
    "runtime": 633.0280029773712
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob081.pddl",
    "runtime": 678.523583650589
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob082.pddl",
    "runtime": 681.4410653114319
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob084.pddl",
    "runtime": 667.2953629493713
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob083.pddl",
    "runtime": 671.5640208721161
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob086.pddl",
    "runtime": 672.8639307022095
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob085.pddl",
    "runtime": 673.9190838336945
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob087.pddl",
    "runtime": 671.9721381664276
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob088.pddl",
    "runtime": 674.4174847602844
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob089.pddl",
    "runtime": 674.5545687675476
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob091.pddl",
    "runtime": 667.121830701828
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob090.pddl",
    "runtime": 667.5867528915405
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob092.pddl",
    "runtime": 661.9887225627899
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob093.pddl",
    "runtime": 666.1930630207062
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob094.pddl",
    "runtime": 673.9068803787231
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob095.pddl",
    "runtime": 673.8598532676697
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob096.pddl",
    "runtime": 671.6075103282928
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob097.pddl",
    "runtime": 665.9625256061554
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob098.pddl",
    "runtime": 667.6813519001007
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob099.pddl",
    "runtime": 661.6544218063354
  },
  {
    "config": {
      "k": Infinity,
      "max_time": 300,
      "metric": "p_success",
      "planner": "forbid",
      "selector": "first"
    },
    "num_plans": 0,
    "p_success": 0.0,
    "problem": "/home/caelan/Programs/pddlstream/examples/fault_tolerant/risk_management/risk-pddl/risk/prob100.pddl",
    "runtime": 666.5916821956635
  }
]